Guide to the Frances Hesselbein Papers, 1942-2013 AIS.2013.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Frances Hesselbein Institute Papers, 1942-2014; A.
  - The Peter F. Drucker Foundation, 1990-2003; I.
    - Projects and Programs, 1991-2002; 6.
      - Board Orientation packet, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Managing Accelerated Productivity seminar, August 1993 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Seminar by Satellite planning materials, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Seminar by Satellite workbook, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Seminar by Satellite registrations and responses, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Drucker Foundation media contacts, January 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Book launch invite list, September 24, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Subscriber Survey feedback questionnaire, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Subscriber Survey feedback questionnaire, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Thought Leader articles, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Foundation Projects and Priorities, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Mandel Technology Project outline, May 8, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Membership Campaign information, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Heightened Skills: Advanced Facilitator Training seminar, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Drucker Foundation holiday party remarks, December 14, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Corpedia proposed courses, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Self-Assessment - Women of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in America, June 3, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Presentation transparencies, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Drucker Foundation Self-Assessment Tool materials, 1994-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Drucker Foundation Annual Reports, 1991-2001 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Drucker Foundation floppy disks, 1990s (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - The Leader to Leader Institute, 2003-2011; II.
    This series contains board meeting materials, management reports, event plans, correspondence, legal and financial documents, annual reports, potential partnership information of the Leader to Leader Institute. The materials are dated from 2003-2011, after which the name of the organization was changed again to the Frances Hesselbein Leadership Institute, though its focus remained the same. Researchers should refer to Series VIII of this subgroup for A/V material relating to the Leader to Leader Institute.
    - Administrative Materials, 2003-2011; 1.
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 9, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Board of Governors meeting, May 5, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 28, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Board of Governors meeting, December 18, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 23, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Board of Governors meeting, May 23, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 26, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Board of Governors meeting, December 14, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 14, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Board of Governors meeting, May 23, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 11, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Board of Governors meeting, December 15, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Board of Governors meeting, January 30, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Resolutions, January 2006 - May 2006 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Board of Governors meeting, June 6, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 18, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 27, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Board of Governors meeting, June 19, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 25, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Board of Governors meeting, December 13, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 12, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Board of Governors meeting, June 2, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 22, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Board of Governors meeting, December 18, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 24, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Board of Governors meeting, June 23, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 22, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Board of Governors meeting, February 23, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Board of Governors meeting, June 22, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Board of Governors meeting, September 21, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Board of Governors meeting materials, December 15, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Summaries of Action and Meeting minutes, 2003-2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Board of Governors Self-Assessment and Retreat, September 11, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Finance Committee meeting, February 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Finance Committee meeting, June 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Program Committee meeting, February 27, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Program Committee meeting, June 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Leader to Leader staff materials, 2006-2010 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Leader to Leader brochure, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Legal documents, 2003-2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Financial statements, 2003-2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Tax information, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Fund Development Report, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Leader to Leader Board Correspondence, 2003-2011 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Projects and Programs, 2003-2011; 2.
      - Meeting the Collaboration Challenge presentation, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Shine a Light dinner, April 20, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - BoardSource/Leader to Leader partnership, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Leadership Working Group materials, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Leader to Leader annual reports, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Drucker Self-Assessment Tool, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Self-Assessment Tool training workbook, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Leader to Leader website archives, 2003-2011 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Publication cover images, June 3, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Program contacts, 2000s (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Leader of the Future Award dinner, October 24, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Leader of the Future Award dinner, October 9, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Drucker Innovation Award dinner, November 19, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Leader of the Future Award dinner poster proofs, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Leader of the Future Award dinner, November 5, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Leader of the Future Award dinner, October 11, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Leader of the Future Award plans and materials, June 2011 - November 2011 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Frances Hesselbein Leadership Institute, 2011-2013; III.
    This series contains fundraising information for the Frances Hesselbein Leadership Institute, as well as legal documents for the organization's name change from the Leader to Leader Institute. There is also correspondence, event plans and invitations, and some financial information. The documents in this series are dated from 2012-2013. Audio/Visual material from this organization is available in Series VIII of this subgroup.
    - Hesselbein Institute name/brand change, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Hesselbein Institute position descriptions, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Website information, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Hesselbein Institute Leadership Exchange grant, 2011-2012 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Leader of the Future Award dinner, October 16, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Publications, 1985-2014; IV.
    This series includes a variety of different publications, including books, workbooks, journals, and some magazines, dated from 1985-2014. The books include those published by the Drucker Foundation and Leader to Leader Institute and are featured in a variety of languages. They are organized chronologically by publication date, though if numerous versions of the same copy existed, these copies were placed together. The series also contains information from various management seminars. Some are products of the Drucker Foundation, while others are from outside nonprofit organizations with which the Drucker Foundation worked. The outside publications provide a sample of the various organizations with which the Drucker Foundation and its later iterations interacted. Many of the documents deal with the Drucker Foundation's Self-Assessment Tool. This series also contains information on the publication of some of these items, specifically those dealing with the Drucker Foundation and later the Leader to Leader Institute.
    - Drucker Foundation, 1991-2006; 1.
      - Drucker Foundation - Leadership Wisdom, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Drucker Foundation News - various issues, 1991-2002 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Drucker Foundation News, 1991-1997 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Drucker Foundation News, March 1998 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Drucker Foundation News, July - August 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Drucker Foundation News, October 1998 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Drucker Foundation News, December 1998 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Drucker Foundation News, April 1999 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Drucker Foundation News, July 1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Drucker Foundation News, November 1999 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Drucker Foundation News, January 2000 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Drucker Foundation News ideas, Summer 2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Drucker Foundation News, January 2001 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
      - Drucker Foundation News, June 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Drucker Foundation News, October 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
      - Drucker Foundation Workbooks, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Self-Assessment Tool workbook and guide, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Self-Assessment Tool (Chinese translation), 2001 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - The Organization of the Future plans, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - The Leader of the Future (Portuguese translation), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
      - The Leader of the Future, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - The Leader of the Future, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
      - The Leader of the Future (German translation), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
      - The Leader of the Future (Spanish translation), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - The Leader of the Future (Korean translation), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
      - The Leader of the Future (Japanese translation), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - The Leader of the Future (Chinese translation), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
      - The Organization of the Future, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14-15)
      - The Organization of the Future (German translation), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 16-17)
      - The Organization of the Future (Spanish translation), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 18-19)
      - The Organization of the Future (Portuguese translation), 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - The Organization of the Future (Korean translation), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 21-22)
      - The Organization of the Future (Portuguese translation), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23-24)
      - The Organization of the Future (Japanese translation), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25-26)
      - The Organization of the Future (Polish translation), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27-28)
      - The Community of the Future, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
      - The Community of the Future (Portuguese translation), 1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - The Drucker Foundation Self-Assessment Tool (Japanese translation), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
      - The Drucker Foundation Self-Assessment Tool (Japanese translation), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - The Drucker Foundation Self-Assessment Tool (Portuguese translation), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
      - Leader to Leader, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Leader to Leader (Portuguese translation), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
      - Leader to Leader (Chinese translation), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
      - Leader to Leader (Chinese translation), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls (Chinese translation), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls (Portuguese translation), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls (Russian translation), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls (French translation), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Leading for Innovation, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - On Mission and Leadership, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - On Mission and Leadership (Chinese translation), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
      - On Mission and Leadership (Indonesian translation), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 27-28)
      - On High-Performance Organizations, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - On High-Performance Organizations (Chinese translation), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 30-31)
      - On High-Performance Organizations (Indonesian translation), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 32-33)
      - On Leading Change, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - On Leading Change (Chinese translation), 2004 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - On Leading Change (Indonesian translation), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 36-37)
      - On Creativity, Innovation, and Renewal, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
      - On Creativity, Innovation, and Renewal (Chinese translation), 2004 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
      - On Creativity, Innovation, and Renewal (Indonesian translation), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 5-6)
        Dates extend beyond time of Drucker Foundation because of later foreign editions of Drucker Foundation books.
    - Leader to Leader Institute, 2005-2014; 2.
      - Five Drucker Questions drafts, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Leader to Leader journal publication correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Leader to Leader journal, 2005-2014 (Box 11, Folder 16-18)
      - The Leader of the Future 2, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
      - The Leader of the Future 2 (Korean translation), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
      - Leader to Leader 2, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 11-12)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 13-14)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization (Russian translation), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization (German translation), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization (Japanese translation), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization (Korean translation), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 19-20)
      - The Five Most Important Questions You Will Ever Ask About Your Organization (Vietnamese translation), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
      - The Organization of the Future 2 (Chinese translation), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 23-24)
      - Be Know Do: Leadership the Army Way (Korean translation), 2007 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
      - Be Know Do: Leadership the Army Way (Japanese translation), 2010 (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
    - Frances Hesselbein Institute, 2012-2013; 3.
      - Leader to Leader journal publication correspondence, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Leader to Leader journal draft copies, 2012-2013 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Outside publications, 1985-2012; 4.
      - Managing the Non-profit Organization: Practices and Principles, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
      - Managing the Non-profit Organization: Practices and Principles (Polish translation), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Managing the Non-profit Organization: Practices and Principles (Bulgarian translation), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Managing the Nonprofit Organization: Practices and Principles (Catalan translation), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - On Leaders and Leadership (Dutch translation), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - Creativity and Innovation (Korean and English text), 2008 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Ashoka-McKinsey Alliance, 1998-2001 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - BoardSource, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - Boundary Crossers, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - Bright China Management Institute, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - Campbell Leadership Descriptor workbook, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - Center for Creative Leadership guidebooks, 2001-2010 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Center for Creative Leadership Visual Explorer, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 27-29)
      - The Conference Board annual reports, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Common Ground magazine, October 2010 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Conversations on Philanthropy, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Creating and Implementing Your Strategic Plan, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - De Pree Leadership Center, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - The Diversity Task Force Exercise, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Drucker Management magazine, 1993-1998 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Executive Book Summaries, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - FOCUS - Using Peter Drucker's Five Questions facilitator's guide, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Fundación Compromiso self-assessment tool, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Fundación Compromiso, 2001-2004 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
      - Global Business Network, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Harvard Business Review, 1996-2009 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Harvard Business School, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Harvard Center for Public Leadership, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - The Human Spirit Initiative monographs, 2000s (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Images of the Past: Portraits of Diversity, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Independent Sector: Building Community, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Jossey-Bass management guidebooks, 1998-2001 (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
      - Leadership Practices Inventory participant workbook, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Learning Styles Inventory, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Leaders on Ethics chapters, 2004-2007 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Making More than Money, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Managing Change in Organizations, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Mapping the Future of Your Association, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Marketing Workbook for Nonprofits, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Marketing Workbook for Nonprofits Vol. II, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - McKinsey Quarterly Anthology: A New Era for Nonprofits, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - National Leadership Index, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - NEXUS: Pittsburgh Dialogues, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - NPO Management Review, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - The Organization of Hope community development workbook, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - James O'Toole - Reconceptualizing the Corporation, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - Pew Partnership - What We Know Works, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Peter Drucker Management Center Executive Collection, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - PolicyLink report, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Racing Toward Diversity, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Sasakawa Peace Foundation symposium report, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Social Purpose and Venture Philanthropy in the New Millennium Vol. 1, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Social Purpose Enterprises and Venture Philanthropy Vol. 2-3, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - The State Education Standard, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Venture Philanthropy Partners - Effective Capacity Building in Nonprofits, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - What a Difference Nonprofits Make, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - White House Fellows, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - World Association of Girl Guides and Girl Scouts - World Issues, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - World Pulse magazine, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - The Seventh Prism workbook, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - The Seventh Prism card set, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Strategic Planning for Nonprofit Organizations, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Publication contracts, 1995-2010 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Jossey-Bass correspondence, 2004-2012 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - John Wiley & Sons correspondence, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Press, 1979-2009; V.
    This series contains all press and news articles on Peter Drucker, The Drucker Foundation, The Leader to Leader Institute, and projects and programs planned by the organizations. The material is dated from 1979-2009, with the bulk of the material focusing on the 1990s and the early 2000s. The Peter Drucker subseries includes obituaries and tributes published after Drucker's death, which accounts for the posthumous dating.
    - Peter F. Drucker, 1979-2009; 1.
      - Peter Drucker news articles, 1979-2009 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Peter Drucker interviews, 1981-2001 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Drucker Interviews, 2001-2005 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Peter Drucker tributes, 2005-2009 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - The Nonprofit Drucker press and materials, 1989-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Peter F. Drucker Foundation, 1990-2002; 2.
      - Drucker Foundation press articles, 1990-2002 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Philippine trip press, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Hesselbein Fellows press, 1998-2002 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Jossey-Bass publicity plans, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Drucker Innovation Award press, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Drucker Foundation conference press, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Drucker Innovation Award press, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Drucker Foundation conference press, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Drucker Foundation conference press, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Drucker Innovation Award press, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Drucker Foundation 2001 conference press (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Drucker Foundation conference press, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Drucker Foundation website press, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Leader of the Future press, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Organization of the Future press, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Community of the Future press, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Leader to Leader book press, 1999-2001 (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Leader to Leader book interview materials, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Leading Beyond the Walls press, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Wisdom in Action series press, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - The Collaboration Challenge press, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - The 5 Most Important Questions... press, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Drucker Self-Assessment Tool press, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Leader to Leader journal press, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Leader to Leader journal press, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Leader to Leader journal press, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Leader to Leader Institute, 2002-2008; 3.
      - Leader to Leader Institute press articles, 2002-2008 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Leader to Leader Institute press folder materials, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Peter F. Drucker files, 1942-2011; VI.
    This series contains information on Peter F. Drucker. There are also articles written by/about Drucker, interviews, correspondence, information on a Drucker documentary, information on Drucker's Presidential Medal of Freedom, speech information and transcripts, and information on the Peter Drucker Archives at Claremont Graduate School in California. The material is dated from 1942-2011, though the bulk of the material is from the 1980s to the early 2000s. Press materials on Peter Drucker may be found in Series V of this subgroup.
    - Harvard Business Review, 1989-2004 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Wall Street Journal articles, 1979-2004 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Articles by Peter Drucker, 1942-2004 (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    - Philanthropy Magazine interview materials, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "Shine a Light" interview, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 9)